CATHERINE **DENNISTON**

(956) 454-5773 · 680 W Sam Houston Pkwy S, Apt. 322 · Houston, TX 77042 dennistonc@gmail.com · https://dennistonc.github.io/portfolio

I have experience in the utilization of multimedia abilities; I create assets that promote customer engagement, retention, and ultimately drive web traffic. With a degree in media production and strong artistic insight, I bring a proficient and passionate approach to web, graphic, and video services. I hope to provide skills, creativity, and innovation with a strong attention to detail.

Experience

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | REYNOLDS & REYNOLDS | DATES FROM 2017 - PRESENT

- · Managed graphical assets to ensure the quality and accuracy in the final product
- Transitioned hundreds of client accounts to responsive web development (emails and newsletters) using proprietary software
- Fast-paced email marketing environment, prioritized more than 10 projects at a time while still meeting deadlines
- Guaranteed products met overall brand and web standards
- · Worked with marketing analysts to bring client ideas to life based on marketing goals that had been set
- · Utilized HTML and Adobe Suite to create email communications

FREELANCE VIDEO PRODUCER | COOL CITY TRADING | DATES FROM 2016, 2018

- · Responsible for creating video content showcasing various products to display on website
- · Met quick deadlines and having videos produced with quick turnaround
- · Went through pre-production to post-production with client ensuring the final product was what they wanted
- · Worked with client requests and making any changes to cater towards what they envisioned
- · Still photography of products on location to display on website

Internships and Related Experience

Internship | Zenfilm | Dates From Summer 2016 - Fall 2016

Internship | B-Good Studios | Dates From Spring 2016 - Summer 2016

Producer/Camera Op/Editor | El Valle – Short Film | Spring 2015

Producer/Director/Camera Op/Editor | Rush - Short Film | Fall 2015

Camera Op/Lighting | Inside Houston Grand Opera | Fall 2015

Producer/Camera/Editor | Anna Karenina Opera Documentary | Spring 2016

Education

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN COMMUNICATIONS | UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON | 2012 - 2016

- · Major: Media Production
- · Minor: Business Administration
- · Sigma Alpha Iota Member 2015 2016 | PR/Social Media Committee Chair
- · Sigma Phi Omega Member 2016 | Historian Committee Chair

Relevant Skills

· Adobe Premiere Pro CC · Microsoft Office

 $\cdot\;$ Adobe Photoshop CC $\;\;\;\;\;\cdot\;$ Final Cut Pro X

· Adobe Illustrator CC · Social Media Management

 $\cdot\;$ Adobe After Effects CC $\;\;\;\cdot\;$ Production Lighting including Arri Lighting packages

· Adobe InDesign CC · Sony a7riii, Canon DSLRs, Lumix GH4, Black Magic 4K, Panasonic AG80, Sony EX3